[Music] Do
you have insurance? Don't be silly, let's
talk
so what is it Sir, the
set for tomorrow is one of the
traditional products of fwd insurance, so
the focus of it is to give
life insurance coverage, and the set for
tomorrow is by the name, I mean
suggested by the name, you are being set
for tomorrow's uncertainties. Okay, there
he is. I would say that he can
take his name and
you are beautiful, sir, here in the set for
tomorrow product, there are different
variants. Okay, so the good thing
about that is, it depends on the
client's needs, you have choices, you
can choose short-term,
technically medium-term, there's a
whole life or permanent type of set
for tomorrow product, so you said sir,
there is a Short term, you said Short
term, sir. How short is the coverage,
there are 5 years, there are 10 years,
then there is also until Uh age 65,
then the longest one, which is the
product set for tomorrow, Estate
protector, up to age  120 120 years old
Yes, what is that for, Johnny, what is the
age? 120 Yes, yes, there is h 120 Okay, so this
is purely insurance, correct sir,
pure life insurance.
He has no other benefits
other than the life insurance coverage
that is produced.
The life insurance coverage that is
provided is to help with the
repatriation of the body of the insured
regardless of the reason why he is
abroad. That's just the
limitation.
Sir, when terrorism
happens, for example, a terrorist attack
is the cause of that. There is an
evaluation that FWD will do, why in
the first place you were there in
that place. Is there really ongoing
terrorist activity? Okay, so that's all,
but regardless of the reason,
whether you are on vacation, you are an OFW,
or you are just traveling. You go in
for that benefit, okay.
I just heard about this
benefit today. I'm aware, sir. FWD being
a multi-Asia insurance company, the
cost of
reporting the body of a person is really different. No, it's not.
he is unlike the living person who
just book an airfare you can go
back to your country now there are
extra expenses so of course to cover
the additional expenses
fwd put that benefit in the set for
tomorrow product okay so nice nice
overseas benefit I will call so
besides sir there are any other benefits there is
the set for tomorrow ah there is Something is
being given by that Sir terminal assistance already a
benefit technically sir
if you have life insurance coverage
with a set for tomorrow of Php1 million
then you were diagnosed with with a
terminal illness okay what will be done
there is to give in advance the
supposed to be life insurance coverage
because we know that when you are
diagnosed or declared
terminally ill it's just a matter of
days or months before you Actually
passed away okay So how about what ah did
the Lord want him to still be alive e The
benefit has been given the benefit So
it will it means that fwd's obligation
for the coverage and even the life
insurance ah portion of the product is
gone because the
Your terminal illness benefit is so advanced so
let's say that based on the contract
set for tomorrow,
your beneficiaries will receive 1 million if
something happens to you which is death
then instead of dying immediately
terminal illness is the one diagnosed
first right? So that means that the
1 million coverage will be given without
waiting for you to die before
releasing Y in advance for Ah maybe ah
just console me okay You still
have a couple of days or months to live
enjoy your benefit Okay so
while you are still Alive even if you are
terminally ill Ah yes It's difficult because
you might not be that mobile anymore I would say
your movement is limited but you
can still somehow Enjoy the benefit of the
product while you are still alive it
can be your inheritance what is it possible
even if you are still a little bit short
you want those with a bucket list
you want to check then yes it is possible
another benefit I saw
when we searched it was
called child protection
What is this Okay so that benefit is Child Protection benefit
will Uh be
received by beneficiary if both of the
insured person just like for
example me and my spouse died Uh due
to the same accident Okay so together
no matter what he is Ah Ah same accident
then not necessarily immediately died
for example we
both had an accident I was the first then a couple of
Uh weeks or Days Later my spouse
followed then we have a minor
child Okay so the benefit will be doubled
a for example 1 million of the original
benefit listed in the contract
insurance contract will be 2 million
Ah so accident si lang accident
siya ah yeah Yes very specific doun
sa ano kait hindi kait hindi hindi
beneficiary yung for not
listed as beneficiary ah ganito sir
kas Of course when he is not listed
as beneficiary There is someone because for
example we have a child of ah
legal age t he is the
beneficiary we consider
our child a minor for that specific benefit
benefit of the product that yung
that benefit will take effect if there is a
minor not necessarily dapat
siya dapat doon dapat doon dapat beneficiary Okay so it
seems like a tip
Just for our viewers, why is it that even
though he is not
disallowed, it is very rare. I
personally recommend that you put a
minor as a beneficiary in
your insurance policy because he does not have the
capacity to be part of the
contract. I have a
beneficiary or child who is below 18, the
assumption is that
he does not have the capacity to handle the money
correctly. So if your
only beneficiary in the insurance policy
you took out is alone, then
the insurance company will require you
to put a guardian. This means
if you have a family member,
relative, or anyone
you can trust to manage
the insurance proceeds
if something happens to you. They are the
guardians who will be honored when
your beneficiary is a minor. Next,
we saw funeral assistance.
Okay, so for funeral assistance,
within 48 hours from the date of the
insured's death, the fwd will advance the benefit, so
Php1,000. It means,
you just inform the fwd.  Sir, as the
beneficiary of the insured person
has passed away, of course there are
requirements to be given to receive
the full amount of the benefit from
life insurance proceeds, let's say from 1
million, sir, within 48
hours of informing the insured of the debt
of the insured, advance 100,000
for the purpose of of course the
assumption is that the
insured does not have any other pre-need plan, so as part of the
support of the company, there are family
members who are left, advance a
portion of the proceeds for the initial
expenses, then while you are fixing the
document for example death
certificates, other proof that the
insured needs to give the whole amount of claim, at
least they are using
money for the initial funeral
setup when needed. They just
bought a Memorial lot on the spot
because they did not buy it before. So
they can use it like that, sir, so within
48 hours, sir, so they advance benefit
which  will be deducted from the
whole amount of insurance coverage
Yes and that is a big help because and
because if Instead of borrowing ' is it
Pretend there is no no fund because what
happened suddenly So there is no fund
no savings Because there is no preneed e that is a
big deal that they will no longer
borrow correct correct Sir that is so
big assistance he is for the ber
family that Ayun nga ah not full
amount you are like that within the first 48
hours at least there is an advance for
initial expenses that they can use
nice and another sir that is an My news is
he has a premium waiver what is it and how does it
work okay so the premium waiver
again based on the the name the term
of premium waiver for example if 5
years to pay the ah set for tomorrow
his policy within the first within
that contract that you pay for 5 years
if something happens for example
terminal illness within the first 5
years since terminal illness only
since the insured or
policy holder is still alive let's say let's put an
example Out Of The 5 years contract
on the third year he diagnosed a
terminal  illness or permanent disability
total and permanent disability the
remaining 2 years of unpaid premiums
he is Okay so it seems in effect
He no longer has an obligation to fwd to pay
the remaining premiums because
he was diagnosed with terminal
illness or total and permanent
disability the question always sir is
What is it ah What is total and
permanent disability Okay so the
most basic sir that's the explanation there
if you can no longer do the normal
function of a person okay for example
you can no longer bathe by yourself Okay
you need to be dependent on the
support of other people to do your daily
activities okay and that also has a period eh
At least Uh 180 days or more ' because
because you have this sir ah there are
temporary ah the disability is just
Yes you can't function but
you only recovered for 30 days ' can you now be on your
own again ' So is there anything else aside
from the disability ib say You have something you
can't do as a as a normal human
being there is also a duration that
needs to be met so who
will debut as to Who is  The doctor will decide to
diagnose SAO for example, what
fw just said should be the big
hospital in BGC, the ones
that can attest to your situation,
even if it's not in the village, even if it's in the
town, what is a licensed medical
doctor? Okay so on the set for tomorrow,
how much is the minimum insurance
coverage for this? 1 million sir. Actually,
1 million is the minimum insurance coverage
for one of the This is my personal
take on that, sir. No, 1 million is because
now, especially for nowadays, let's just say it's
easy to run out.
Okay, so what I mean by that is that if
you have 1 million insurance
coverage, that's what you leave to
your family member. It's a big help, but
let's be realistic, sir. It won't last
long. Okay, for example, if the
family's monthly expenses are
50,000 per month, then
within a span of 1.5 years,
the 1 million will be gone. What if there was
splurging and the expenses suddenly increased
because someone suddenly received
money? So, it's shorter.  How many years
can you get this set for
tomorrow Sir is allowed
ah ah 55 and 60 Okay so 60 means
before he is rich before he is um
Senior like a senior citizen because to
us that is 60 he can
still be cremated
okay Because when it is a little Ah it is no longer
beneficial Yes I can cover you but
with Uh a significant amount of premium
maybe it is more okay sir this is
our strategy Just save the premium in the bank
for example ah there are many
requirements ' ba let's say that you can no
longer be approved as a regular ah the
assessment you are not a regular client
meaning there are additional Uh premium
because of the condition because of the
age ' ba he needs to be balanced sir
so on my part as an advisor
I will not benefit from it because
I definitely will not
get any Commission if the client does not take it
but on the part of the
the person he will benefit on on
the advice that I gave ' ba of course
we will not stop you if you still want
him to do that freely but
I just need to tell you the
situation that is becoming pros and cons Yeah correct
correct sir if his budget can afford it is
not money that is his decision ' how
many years is the minimum age that can be done
sir the minimum age is as Young as 18
months 18 months Yes So that means baby
is young yes yes but of course Sir There is a
limitation in terms of the Uh
coverage ah the one who will decide that is
the head office because ah there is some
saying what is the reason why you want to be
covered by someone's insurance ' is it
like insurability interest these kinds of
conversations first of all ah that is young or
Said baby There is no
responsibility yet why do you want to
cover a lot Okay so certain
limitations It is possible but there are certain
limitations as to the amount of coverage
po agree it is still a baby then bread
winner what did you do e He was still young he
had an obligation
right away his benefits are good
sir no His benefits are good
the question
ah If there is any disadvantage to
this if there is any What is that Okay so one
of disadvantage when for example for
set for tomorrow at least for that
product That's if not for us ah
we have no benefit to get for example sir
ha based on the coverage up to age  60
or 65 then you outlived what is the
covered period ' did he not have a
return of premium i mean ah fw the
insurance company gave you peace of mind
if something happens to you But that did
n't happen ah Lord took care of
you to be healthy you live until the end
of the coverage you won't receive anything
Returned money So if I can call that as
disadvantage that's all I think sir Because
you didn't take advantage of the
benefit which is for me thankful for
that I would say I was able to live a
long life that's what he was but you said
sir the coverage is until age 120 120
for the specific products sir Estate
protector Ah okay because there are
different variants correct Sir There is shortterm
cover there is income protector then
Estate protector when it comes to state
protector that is a product sir the Focus is
really on those who want to leave
a legacy or Ah that benefit monetary and
protect their Estate because before sir
when the um train law took effect
or the adjustment to tax rates
the Estate tax is a very big issue because before that it was
back then what else was it  Of course, the
more you own an estate, the
more tax you will pay or
your estate when it's time to pass that
to your next generation. Now, it's
only 6%, let's say it's the same
as the sales stock, for example, the
property capital gain
is only 6%, so yes, it's
still beneficial for a person to get an
insurance policy for the reason that it's
not the first one, it's not taxable. The
benefit of life insurance proceeds is not
taxable and it's not subject to
ah. It's like a temporary ii-f of the bank when
someone dies and
the bank informs the bank that their account holder has died,
they will wait for clearance from
the BIR. Before releasing the Uh bank
account of the deceased person to anyone
authorized by the BIR, for example,
let's say, I have, for example, my
father's bank account, just a bank account in
General. Then the bank finds out that
their account holder has passed away, I can't withdraw the money
from the bank. Okay, okay. So I can probably
icon, don't inform them, but that's a
violation.  There needs to be some settling
first if there is a state tax liability,
but the life insurance proceeds go
straight to the beneficiaries. Okay, or it
won't go through the bank because it no longer
belongs to the insured. Correct, correct.
Yes, it's
really for the beneficiaries. Who is
recommended to get this product?
Okay, for Uh, for for, for tomorrow, in
general, this product is suitable
for those who just want to add
insurance coverage. Okay, and for those who do
n't have enough budget for a
comprehensive life and health insurance
policy. For example, let's see,
you're just starting out in business
and you just want peace of mind that if
something happens to you,
your beneficiaries will receive it. Especially if you have
dependents, children, spouses. Is that how it is,
sir? If my memory serves me right,
for as low as I think Php1 or
Php8,000
per year, you can get a 1 million
amount of life insurance coverage if
your age is 30 to 35. Okay, so if the
Let's just say 18,000 per year
That's only 1 1,500 per month okay or
around Php50 per day ' ba So if
your income is relatively not
that high but you want an insurance
coverage for yourself
he's going to be very busy sir ' ba and of course he can be
stretched eh the higher the coverage
that's all the higher the premium that
needs to be paid when what the
policy owner set for tomorrow Is this it
sir what how to
apply Okay for now because sir with
the digitalization then with what
experience with pandemic he can now be used in
two ways first
the products are available digital products by
fwd on the website itself Okay so if you have
a Uh meron kayong known advisor From
fwd You Just ask for the Agent link Okay
so if there is an Agent link because every time
that you buy through that Agent link
your friend who is a
relative of fwd's agent will also benefit because
even if you buy directly
from the website they will still receive the
Commission on the product so the
only benefit is not on both sides is for
example you really want  to decide for
yourself you don't want input even if you're
coming even if you're a person you don't want
pressure that someone is following up
SAO someone is calling ah are you going to get
insurance or what ' ba So you can
purchase directly from the website then it's
also possible sir kunyari Really you don't
know from fwd you can purchase
directly from the website this same
product set for tomorrow available
set for tomorrow available he ah one
way is directly from the agent at
Agents y So whichever you prefer but the
point is just Get insurance
coverage whether through the website or
through a person or sales person
it's possible any variants what's
not just you ah yes yes any any any
variant that's just in
terms of the coverage up to 5 million
only can be purchased coverage
online online but Larger or bigger than
that you have to go through an agent All
right Okay nice Is there a Ong medical
exam He has a medical exam ah like this sir ha
ah when the website because
our viewers buy there are questions
there that I have to they have to answer
truthfully of course the personal
information age  then medical history so
let's just say that ah all there is
Okay say no no no
previous ah disease no
hospitalization recently ' ba hindi na
ire-required ng medical examination
provided that you answer that truthfully
then based on your answer the
assessment of ah by head office is You
are a standard client Meaning no
no additional premium that should be
charged SAO Okay he will have a
medical exam Even if you are all goods if
the coverage you want to buy is too much
for example Uh you go through
an agent then you say Harvey I want
50 million already coverage from set
for tomorrow let's say if he is allowed
then based on your physical condition
based on your declaration you are healthy
but because of the amount of the
coverage that you want to undo you with some
examination and possibly some
questioners Why are you Why do you want
that amount of coverage ' ba then you
just have to explain that this is how
big my property is that I want to be
protected in terms of the Estate
tax top three most important message to
those who have a policy that  What
can you say to them? Okay so top TH
first is continue paying for the policy
Okay so you started that whether 5
years 10 years or whole life to pay
Your set for tomorrow policy make
sure that the lapsation doesn't
go away because for the
benefit of the Viewer who doesn't have an
insurance policy it means that
our benefit under the insurance policy
is gone okay one of the most common
reasons is that the premium has not been paid
'ba So make sure that
your payment continues if
you still have to pay for set for
tomorrow any any or any insurance
product so that your coverage continues
Okay so secondly consider adding
additional Uh insurance especially if
this is the only insurance
policy you have set for tomorrow since
This is focus on really on the life
insurance No health no
other benefits consider adding Okay so
if you already have a budget and can really afford the
finances, add insurance that
includes health comprehensive
health benefits Okay so thirdly is If
you can afford to add it let's say that
you have already met the
I said the first two sir, this is the third one if
you still want additional coverage
coming from the set for tomorrow I
suggest that you do So because that's the good thing
Sir for as long as you can avail
of the cover
of the set for tomorrow, increase
your coverage, increase
your life insurance coverage it means that if
something happens to you the
beneficiaries your loved ones relatives
or any or even those institutions
that you want to benefit for example a church, they
can be charitable
institutions, they can
be beneficiaries of your policy So
you can live a Legacy Okay so now
you can spread it out for example 10
million for your family 5 million for a
charitable institution, you can do
that 'ba Although you don't have that kind of money
in the bank that is multimillion pesos
but because offset set for tomorrow
you can do it, it will be possible
sir okay so what is it, no, getting it
depends on the purpose, it's the correct purpose, that's where
you really go back sir purpose
if you have the top three most important
message
to those who have the product What about
those who don't have this product yet okay
so  no products yet Okay,
just message there sir is ah really You
have to assess first if you need
this product Okay ah What I mean is
that if this is the product
you need you talk to a trusted advisor
whether you know someone or you want
to call fwd directly then that's fine So
assess if you need this
product or if Really You have the
budget k may budget naman kayo sir
you can consult
mayong life insurance benefit merog
health comprehensive health together na
talaga siya So for me that's a complete
insurance policy life and Health Okay so
life and Health really if that can be done right
away Although ah Honestly
his premium is a little higher because of
the benefits you proceed with that This is just
like a set for tomorrow Sir I suggest
this Especially For people who are really
starting out okay not
enough budget ' ba They just want
coverage for them for For The Love one
is perfect Ong ano set for tomorrow So
if in case sir that they want to avail
this how can they ah contact I
have a Facebook account Harvey deus Dash
personal Finance you  can search
I'm probably searchable on Facebook
then I'll also give my personal details
or how to contact me here in what in
our group in ipro so you can reach out
and I'm like this sir Ah Of course
it will benefit me or at least my career
career if I gain clients okay but if
they have a preferred advisor still
ah especially if they are also fwd also
their friends and family members I
would suggest that you go to them because
why are they the people who
trust you sir ' is it to me i am
confident that I can serve you well the
purpose of getting insurance I
definitely can serve you well but if
you have a preferred advisor that Tiga fwd
since discussing fw
products go ba Because the point is sir
you have to have them have
insurance coverage whether you
get it No problem okay so sir
Harvey Thank
you for setting up for tomorrow set up for
tomorrow tayo Thank you
than if you want more content like this
follow ipro
[Music]
cooperative y